

My Contacts

- **(** +38 (096)-846-59-45
- Y Kiyv, Ukraine
- LinkedIn
- Telegram
- ⊕ GitHub

Hard Skills

- Typescript, JavaScript(ES2015-2019)
- React
- HTML5, CSS3, Sass(Scss), BEM, Bootstrap, Bulma.
- Figma
- Redux, Node.sj, Express,
 PostgreSQL, MongoDB
- Git/GitHub, VS Code, Chrome Developer Tools (incl. React), NPM, Webpack
- Trello, Agile, Scrum
- English: upper-Intermediate

Education

 Master's degree in Automation and Computer-Integrated Sciences

Kyiv Polytechnic Institute 2017 - 2023

 Frontend/Fullstack course at Mate academy

Khutorovyi Ivan

Fullstack developer

About Me

I am a full-stack developer with about two years of experience. My tech stack includes **JavaScript**, **React**, **Node**, **Express**, and **SQL**. I graduated from a **technical university** with a specialization in Automation and Computer-Integrated Sciences, where I was first introduced to programming. I have upper-intermediate knowledge of English and continue to attend English classes regularly several times a week. As for myself, I

would describe myself as sociable, versatile, curious, and with a positive outlook on life. I pay close attention to details and constantly strive to improve my results.

Professional Experience

1. Full-stack Developer | Projects May 2023 - present

1. Apple store: <u>Demo</u> <u>Frontend</u> <u>Backend</u>

2. TaskMaster React App: Demo Code

3. Landing Page: Demo Code

Technologies: React.js, Node.js, TypeScript, JS, HTML/SCSS, REST API, PostgreSQL, Express, Postman.

2. Technical Support, Front-end developer | IT-Enterprise March 2021 - May 2023

Key responsibilities:

- Updated the web page to the latest design.
- Engaged in web development.
- Fixed bugs.
- Wrote automated tests using Cypress for the website.
- Acted as a liaison between clients and developers.
- Managed tasks in Trello and followed the Scrum methodology.
- Organized team-building activities in the last year (kayaking, board games)

3. Instructor at McDonald's February 2020 - February 2021

Achievements.:

- Promoted to Instructor within six months while pursuing a university education
- Was in the process of training to become a manager until receiving an offer in the IT field.

Achievements

2015 The best mathematician at the Economics and Mathematics Lyceum.

2018 13 out of 14 places in the KPI Comedy League.

2019 Winner of the "who can drink the most wine without using hands" competition in Hungary.